top of page

* More...

Use tab to navigate through the menu items.

PRIVACY POLICY 
===============

for Rednecks with Paychecks
===========================

This Privacy Policy, which applies to REDNECKS WITH PAYCHECKS and all websites tied to this product, was last updated on 1/20/2017 and placed in force on that date. You hereby explicitly and unambiguously consent to the collection, use and transfer, in electronic or other form, of your personal data as described herein. You understand and hereby affirm that that REDNECKS WITH PAYCHECKS may hold certain personal information about you, including, but not limited to, your name, email address, home address, and telephone number.

REDNECKS WITH PAYCHECKS knowingly collects information required for utilizing our service. Information collected may include your name, address, birthdate, phone, and email address. Information collected may also include customer's names, emails, addresses, and phone numbers. Information about your computer including your IP address, browser type, and access times will be used to help us better serve our customers.

REDNECKS WITH PAYCHECKS does use cookies. However, any and all information collected will not be sold, rented, or leased to any third parties or used to customize advertising. Personal information can be edited at any time by contacting REDNECKS WITH PAYCHECKS by email to edit your account information. We can be reached at [info@redneckswithpaychecks.com](mailto:info@streamticketing.com) or write to REDNECKS WITH PAYCHECKS at PO Box 443, Saint Jo, TX 76265.

Your personal information may be used to allow us to contact you by email to provide information about our events, newsletters, marketing, promotional and other information that may be of interest to you. You can opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications. This can be done by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in any email we send.

REDNECKS WITH PAYCHECKS may share data with trusted third party partners to help us deliver our service to you. This includes vendors that may perform statistical analysis, vendors used to send email and/or paper mail, provide customer support, store and maintain database and website information.

All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to REDNECKS WITH PAYCHECKS and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information. REDNECKS WITH PAYCHECKS does not respond to Do Not Track (DNT) signals. Do Not Track (DNT) is a preference you can set in your web browser's settings. You can manage this setting (enabling or disabling) in the Preferences or Settings menu of your web browser. This will let the websites you visit know that you do not want to be tracked. REDNECKS WITH PAYCHECKS will make every effort to never disclose your personal information. However, information will be disclosed without notice if we are required to do so by law or by legal processes served on REDNECKS WITH PAYCHECKS. REDNECKS WITH PAYCHECKS does not knowingly collect personal information of children under 13 years of age. Changes to this Privacy Policy may be occasionally applied. We encourage you to check back regularly to insure you are informed how your information is used and protected.

​

Get the Official RWP newsletter in your email inbox. Don't miss out! Sign up!

Sign Me Up!

Rednecks With Paychecks

P.O. Box 443 • Saint Jo, Texas 76265

877-RWP-4FUN

©2024 Rednecks With Paychecks Off-Road, LLC. Rednecks With Paychecks, Rednecks With Paychecks Off-Road, and RWP OFFROAD are registered trademarks of Rednecks With Paychecks Off-Road, LLC. All rights reserved.

bottom of page
